const questionBank = [
  [
    {
      question:
        "Groups of four words are given. In each group, one word is correctly spelt. Find the correctly spelt word and mark your answer in the Answer-Sheet.",
      options: ["Aquarim", "Aquarium", "Acquariam", "Acquerium"],
      answer: "Aquarium",
      id: 1,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Groups of four words are given. In each group, one word is correctly spelt. Find the correctly spelt word and mark your answer in the Answer-Sheet.",
      options: ["Fasimmile", "Facsimile", "Fasimile", "Fascimilee"],
      answer: "Facsimile",
      id: 2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Direction: In the following questions, a sentence has been given in Active voice. Out of the four alternatives suggested, select the one which best expresses the same sentence in Passive voice.",
      options: [
        "Who had done this work?",
        "Who did this work?",
        "Who has done this work?",
        "Who does this work?",
      ],
      answer: "Who did this work?",
      id: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "How would one say goodybye in spainsh?",
      options: ["Adios", "Halo", "Au Revior", "sair"],
      answer: "Adios",
      id: 4,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which best selling Toy in 1983 caused hysteria, resulting riots breaking stores?",
      options: [
        "Cabbage patch kid",
        "Transformers",
        "Care Bears",
        "Rubik's Cube",
      ],
      answer: "Care Bears",
      id: 5,
    },
  ],

  [
    {
      question:
        "The total number of digits used in numbering the pages of a book of 366 pages is.",
      options: ["732", "990", "1098", "1305"],
      answer: "990",
      id: 1,
    },

    {
      question:
        "There are Rs.300 in a box in denomination of Rs.1, 50 paisa and 25 paisa and in the ratio 2:4:8. Find the number of coins of 25 paisa ",
      options: ["300", "200", "400", "100"],
      answer: "400",
      id: 2,
    },

    {
      question: "If 2A=3B=4C, then A:B:C will be- ",
      options: ["2:3:4", "4:3:2", "6:4:3", "3:4:6"],
      answer: "6:4:3",
      id: 3,
    },
    {
      question:
        "There are Rs.300 in a box in denomination of Rs.1, 50 paisa and 25 paisa and in the ratio 2:4:8. Find the number of coins of 25 paisa ",
      options: ["300", "200", "400", "100"],
      answer: "400",
      id: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "If 2A=3B=4C, then A:B:C will be- ",
      options: ["2:3:4", "4:3:2", "6:4:3", "3:4:6"],
      answer: "6:4:3",
      id: 5,
    },
  ],
];
